https://www.powerdrives.com/privacy-policy/

Power Drives, Inc.’s Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy will explain how our organization uses the personal data we collect from you when you use our website.Topics:What data do we collect?How do we collect your data?How will we use your data?How do we store your data?MarketingWhat are your data protection rights?What are cookies?How do we use cookies?What types of cookies do we use?How to manage your cookiesPrivacy policies of other websitesChanges to our privacy policyHow to contact usHow to contact the appropriate authoritiesWhat data do we collect?Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) collects the following data:Personal identification information (Name, email address, phone number, etc.)How do we collect your data?You directly provide Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) with most of the data we collect. We collect data and process data when you:Register online or place an order for any of our products or services.Voluntarily complete a customer survey or provide feedback on any of our message boards or via email.Use or view our website via your browser’s cookies.How will we use your data?Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) collects your data so that we can:Process your order and manage your account.Email you with special offers on other products and services we think you might like.Track our website trafficIf you agree, Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) will share your data with our partner companies so that they may offer you their products and services. When Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) processes your order, it may send your data to, and also use the resulting information from, credit reference agencies to prevent fraudulent purchases.How do we store your data?Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) securely stores your data from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Power Drives, Inc. uses the following:Network Solutions Certification AuthorityGo Daddy Certification AuthorityWhen personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.MarketingPower Drives, Inc. (PDI) would like to send you information about products and services of ours that we think you might like, as well as those of our partner companies.This website uses Mouseflow: a website analytics tool that provides session replay, heatmaps, funnels, form analytics, feedback campaigns, and similar features/functionality. Mouseflow may record your clicks, mouse movements, scrolling, form fills (keystrokes) in non-excluded fields, pages visited and content, time on site, browser, operating system, device type (desktop/tablet/phone), screen resolution, visitor type (first time/returning), referrer, anonymized IP address, location (city/country), language, and similar meta data. Mouseflow does not collect any information on pages where it is not installed, nor does it track or collect information outside your web browser. If you’d like to opt-out, you can do so at https://mouseflow.com/opt-out. If you’d like to obtain a copy of your data, make a correction, or have it erased, please contact us first or, as a secondary option, contact Mouseflow at privacy@mouseflow.com.For more information, see Mouseflow’s Privacy Policy at http://mouseflow.com/privacy/.
For more information on Mouseflow and GDPR, visit https://mouseflow.com/gdpr/.
For more intormation on Mouseflow and CCPA visit https://mouseflow.com/ccpaIf you have agreed to receive marketing, you may always opt out at a later date.You have the right at any time to stop Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) from contacting you for marketing purposes or giving your data to other members of the Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) Group.If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please click here.What are your data protection rights?Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:The right to access – You have the right to request Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) for copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.The right to rectification – You have the right to request that Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) to complete the information you believe is incomplete.The right to erasure – You have the right to request that Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) erase your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.The right to data portability – You have the right to request that Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us at our email:Call us at: 800.888.1373Or write to us: marketing133@powerdrives.comCookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technologyFor further information, visit allaboutcookies.org.How do we use cookies?Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) uses cookies in a range of ways to improve your experience on our website, including:Keeping you signed inUnderstanding how you use our websiteWhat types of cookies do we use?There are a number of different types of cookies, however, our website uses:Functionality – Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) uses these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences. These could include what language you prefer and location you are in. A mix of first-party and third-party cookies are used.Advertising – Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) uses these cookies to collect information about your visit to our website, the content you viewed, the links you followed and information about your browser, device, and your IP address. Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) sometimes shares some limited aspects of this data with third parties for advertising purposes. We may also share online data collected through cookies with our advertising partners. This means that when you visit another website, you may be shown advertising based on your browsing patterns on our website.How to manage cookiesYou can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.Privacy policies of other websitesThe Power Drives, Inc. (PDI) website contains links to other websites. Our privacy policy applies only to our website, so if you click on a link to another website, you should read their privacy policy.Changes to our privacy policyPower Drives, Inc. (PDI) keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on 30 January 2020.How to contact usIf you have any questions about Power Drives, Inc. (PDI)’s privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us.Email us at: webgeneral@powerdrives.comCall us: 800.888.1373Or write to us at: 801 Exchange St. | Buffalo, NY 14210
News & Updates
Careers
PowerHouse™ Fuel Savings Calculator
Contact UsPowerHouse Portal5 Convenient Express Hose Center LocationsHomeProductsHydraulicsPneumaticsIndustrial HoseLocomotiveDiesel Engine BackServices & CapabilitiesHose AssembliesHose-Tube CombinationsVendor Managed InventoryTube BendingEnd FormingKittingEngineering & Support ServicesAfter-Hours Emergency ServicesAir Dryer Piping Kits BackMarkets and IndustriesAgricultureConstruction & MiningDiesel EngineFood & BeverageInjection MoldingLocomotiveMarineMaterial HandlingMunicipalityOil & Gas BackResourcesNewsQuality AssurancePowerHouse™ Fuel Savings CalculatorLiteratureVideo Library BackAbout UsCareersHistory Back
× Close Panel
